{
    "id": "7e87e0cd54a94654aeefc3d88e5db85c",
    "title": "Sentence Completion Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I don’t care ……………….. your opinion.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "for",
                "with",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I’m sorry, I broke the vase – I ………………… help it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "could",
                "couldn't",
                "couldn't have",
                "can't"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Who takes ……………….. the sick?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "care of",
                "care after",
                "care about"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She is a selfish woman, but you still …………………..  her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can't help liking",
                "can help liking",
                "can't help but liking",
                "help can't liking"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I am the happiest man ...................... the world.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "of",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The apartment ………………… I live is very small.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "where",
                "that",
                "which",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven’t bought the ticket. I haven’t ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "also",
                "neither",
                "too"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The books ………………… all over the floor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "were laying",
                "were lying",
                "laid",
                "were laid"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I always have trouble …………………  faces.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to remember",
                "remembering",
                "remember",
                "to remembering"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It …………………. since yesterday morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is snowing",
                "was snowing",
                "has been snowing",
                "had been snowing"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}